<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>What We Offer on FEOTA - Consultancy and Tutoring</title>
    <link>https://feota.eu/</link>
    <description>Recent content in What We Offer on FEOTA - Consultancy and Tutoring</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 21:50:57 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://feota.eu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Education consulting</title>
      <link>https://feota.eu/services/education-consultancy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 02:32:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://feota.eu/services/education-consultancy/</guid>
      <description>We carefully developed our education consulting service packages for enthusiastic science students to get into their dream universities.
Our expert consultants are themselves graduates from the top ranking universities in Finland; a country well-known for its best education system. Therefore, not only that you get step-by-step guidance to properly arrange admission and visa related documents but also valuable tips to improve your motivation letter and an opportunity to learn more about the country you are willing to visit for higher education.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best education</title>
      <link>https://feota.eu/finland/best_education/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://feota.eu/finland/best_education/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review1</title>
      <link>https://feota.eu/reviews/review1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://feota.eu/reviews/review1/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;I received my maths exam result and got the extra point, so I will now graduate! Thank you so much for all your help Shirajum.&amp;quot;
-Ella, IB maths</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Career consulting</title>
      <link>https://feota.eu/services/career-consultancy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://feota.eu/services/career-consultancy/</guid>
      <description>Our career consultants are there to help you understand the pros and cons of different career tracks in STEM and make a realistic plan.
With the rapid advancement of science and technology, the skills required for job positions in the field of STEM is evolving too. On top of that, specific expertise is needed to succeed in landing a job in some of these fields. No one can help you better than someone who already built a career in STEM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Click here to see the infographics</title>
      <link>https://feota.eu/scicore/infographics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://feota.eu/scicore/infographics/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happiest country in the world</title>
      <link>https://feota.eu/finland/happiest_country/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://feota.eu/finland/happiest_country/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review2</title>
      <link>https://feota.eu/reviews/review2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://feota.eu/reviews/review2/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;As a tutor, Shirajum is excellent, cooperative and sincere. I give her 100 out of 100.&amp;quot;
-Afzal, IELTS</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Click here to read science facts</title>
      <link>https://feota.eu/scicore/facts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://feota.eu/scicore/facts/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review3</title>
      <link>https://feota.eu/reviews/review3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://feota.eu/reviews/review3/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Ms. Shirajum is an excellent math tutor. She explains all the concepts constructively and breaks them down for better understanding. She is also willing to go over the concepts multiple times if I am having trouble understanding the problems at first. I definitely recommend her as a math tutor for everyone.&amp;quot;
-Ankita, IB maths</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Safest country</title>
      <link>https://feota.eu/finland/safest_country/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://feota.eu/finland/safest_country/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tutoring</title>
      <link>https://feota.eu/services/asktutor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://feota.eu/services/asktutor/</guid>
      <description>AskTutor is an unique service we developed, keeping students from diverse background and their individual needs in mind.
We offer high quality physics, chemistry, mathematics, biology and English language tuition at an affordable price. You have the freedom to choose any number of sessions per month. Private tuition can be arranged either online (for students living outside Helsinki region) or in-person (for students living within Helsinki region) depending on the availability, area of expertise and location of the tutors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Click here to read our blogs</title>
      <link>https://feota.eu/scicore/blogs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://feota.eu/scicore/blogs/</guid>
      <description>This page is still under construction. Please visit later!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital forerunner</title>
      <link>https://feota.eu/finland/digital_forerunner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://feota.eu/finland/digital_forerunner/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Click here to watch our videos</title>
      <link>https://feota.eu/scicore/videos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://feota.eu/scicore/videos/</guid>
      <description>This page is still under construction. Please come back later!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Student healthcare</title>
      <link>https://feota.eu/finland/student_healthcare/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://feota.eu/finland/student_healthcare/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cleanest air</title>
      <link>https://feota.eu/finland/cleanest_air/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://feota.eu/finland/cleanest_air/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About us</title>
      <link>https://feota.eu/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://feota.eu/about/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://feota.eu/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://feota.eu/faq/</guid>
      <description>About Heading   Frequently Asked Questions  Which countries do you cover in Europe?
&amp;ndash; At present, we cover Finland, Denmark, Norway, Germany and Switzerland only.
Is FEOTA a legitimate consulting service?
&amp;ndash; Yes, FEOTA Oy (business ID 3225816-1) is a company registered in the Finnish trade register (Kaupparekisteri).
Where is FEOTA&amp;rsquo;s office located?
&amp;ndash; Our main office is located at Kirkkonummi, capital region of Finland. We do not have any other branches or business affiliates or business partners anywhere else in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://feota.eu/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://feota.eu/privacy/</guid>
      <description>About Heading  FEOTA Oy Privacy Policy  Federation of Experts On Theoretical &amp;amp; Applied Sciences, also known as FEOTA Oy, is a limited liability company (Osakeyhtiö) based in Finland. FEOTA’s Privacy Policy complies with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), applicable as of 25 May 2018, in all member states to harmonize data privacy laws across Europe. To access the official PDF of the Regulation (EU) 2016/679 (General Data Protection Regulation), visit GDPR page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prohibited Conduct</title>
      <link>https://feota.eu/prohibited-conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://feota.eu/prohibited-conduct/</guid>
      <description>About Heading  Prohibited Conduct FEOTA Oy Last update on: Feb 23, 2022
  Impersonating Us or Our personnel or another person in order to trick, defraud, disparage, tarnish, harm, harass, or mislead Us or others, especially in any attempt to retrieve sensitive information or conspire against Us or gain monetary benefit. Harass, threat, intimidate, annoy or bully Us, or Our Personnel or others on Our Platforms. Offering any sort of bribery, or monetary gifts or something of value to Us or Our personnel in order to gain extra facilities outside of the agreed compensations for Our services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms of Service</title>
      <link>https://feota.eu/terms-of-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://feota.eu/terms-of-service/</guid>
      <description>About Heading  Terms of Service FEOTA Oy
Published on: Feb 24, 2022
Last update on: Feb 24, 2022
 It is important that you read this Terms of Service carefully before using our services to know what you can expect from us and what we expect from you.
 Interpretation and Definitions  Interpretation The words of which the initial letter is capitalized have meanings defined under the following conditions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms of Use Consultancy</title>
      <link>https://feota.eu/terms-of-use-consultancy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://feota.eu/terms-of-use-consultancy/</guid>
      <description>About Heading  Terms of Use FEOTA Consultancy Last update on: Feb 24, 2022
The general guidelines are Our policies that must be respected by all the Users of FEOTA Consultancy. The special guidelines are Our policies for individual consulting service meant for the Users of that particular service only.
 General guidelines  The consulting sessions are always arranged online between the Consultant and the Customer. Confirmed session(s) can only be canceled 5 business days prior to the meeting time without any cancellation fee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms of Use Tutoring</title>
      <link>https://feota.eu/terms-of-use-tutoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://feota.eu/terms-of-use-tutoring/</guid>
      <description>About Heading  Terms of Use FEOTA AskTutor
Last update: Feb 20, 2022
 Every Customer gets a 25 minutes-long introductory session free of charge as a courtesy of their first time purchase of Our tutoring services. The introductory session is always arranged online between the Tutor and the Customer.
 Face-to-face tuition  The price of a one-hour session includes the base hourly fee, compensation for the Tutor’s trip for up to 10 km from his/her place of residence to the agreed location, and a VAT of 24%.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
