<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on FEOTA - Consultancy and Tutoring</title>
    <link>https://feota.eu/pages/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on FEOTA - Consultancy and Tutoring</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://feota.eu/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About us</title>
      <link>https://feota.eu/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://feota.eu/about/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://feota.eu/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://feota.eu/faq/</guid>
      <description>About Heading   Frequently Asked Questions  Which countries do you cover in Europe?
&amp;ndash; At present, we cover Finland, Denmark, Norway, Germany and Switzerland only.
Is FEOTA a legitimate consulting service?
&amp;ndash; Yes, FEOTA Oy (business ID 3225816-1) is a company registered in the Finnish trade register (Kaupparekisteri).
Where is FEOTA&amp;rsquo;s office located?
&amp;ndash; Our main office is located at Kirkkonummi, capital region of Finland. We do not have any other branches or business affiliates or business partners anywhere else in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://feota.eu/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://feota.eu/privacy/</guid>
      <description>About Heading  FEOTA Oy Privacy Policy  Federation of Experts On Theoretical &amp;amp; Applied Sciences, also known as FEOTA Oy, is a limited liability company (Osakeyhtiö) based in Finland. FEOTA’s Privacy Policy complies with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), applicable as of 25 May 2018, in all member states to harmonize data privacy laws across Europe. To access the official PDF of the Regulation (EU) 2016/679 (General Data Protection Regulation), visit GDPR page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prohibited Conduct</title>
      <link>https://feota.eu/prohibited-conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://feota.eu/prohibited-conduct/</guid>
      <description>About Heading  Prohibited Conduct FEOTA Oy Last update on: Feb 23, 2022
  Impersonating Us or Our personnel or another person in order to trick, defraud, disparage, tarnish, harm, harass, or mislead Us or others, especially in any attempt to retrieve sensitive information or conspire against Us or gain monetary benefit. Harass, threat, intimidate, annoy or bully Us, or Our Personnel or others on Our Platforms. Offering any sort of bribery, or monetary gifts or something of value to Us or Our personnel in order to gain extra facilities outside of the agreed compensations for Our services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms of Service</title>
      <link>https://feota.eu/terms-of-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://feota.eu/terms-of-service/</guid>
      <description>About Heading  Terms of Service FEOTA Oy
Published on: Feb 24, 2022
Last update on: Feb 24, 2022
 It is important that you read this Terms of Service carefully before using our services to know what you can expect from us and what we expect from you.
 Interpretation and Definitions  Interpretation The words of which the initial letter is capitalized have meanings defined under the following conditions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms of Use Consultancy</title>
      <link>https://feota.eu/terms-of-use-consultancy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://feota.eu/terms-of-use-consultancy/</guid>
      <description>About Heading  Terms of Use FEOTA Consultancy Last update on: Feb 24, 2022
The general guidelines are Our policies that must be respected by all the Users of FEOTA Consultancy. The special guidelines are Our policies for individual consulting service meant for the Users of that particular service only.
 General guidelines  The consulting sessions are always arranged online between the Consultant and the Customer. Confirmed session(s) can only be canceled 5 business days prior to the meeting time without any cancellation fee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms of Use Tutoring</title>
      <link>https://feota.eu/terms-of-use-tutoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://feota.eu/terms-of-use-tutoring/</guid>
      <description>About Heading  Terms of Use FEOTA AskTutor
Last update: Feb 20, 2022
 Every Customer gets a 25 minutes-long introductory session free of charge as a courtesy of their first time purchase of Our tutoring services. The introductory session is always arranged online between the Tutor and the Customer.
 Face-to-face tuition  The price of a one-hour session includes the base hourly fee, compensation for the Tutor’s trip for up to 10 km from his/her place of residence to the agreed location, and a VAT of 24%.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
